Hello Hello Friends, in today's video I am going to
tell you
how you can check your loan finance on a two wheeler. Like
sometimes you buy a second hand two
wheeler vehicle and you do
not know whether there is finance on it or
not, so in today's video I am going to tell you in a very easy
way
how you can check the loan finance on any two wheeler vehicle.
So do like the video and do
not skip it at all. Also,
if you are new to this channel, then subscribe to the channel
and press the bell icon so that
you keep getting notifications of upcoming videos. Now
open any browser on your mobile screen.
I open the Chrome browser.
In the search bar, you have to type Hero
Fincorp.
After tapping on the button, we will search and the
first website will appear in front of you.
www.com. We will click on it.
After clicking it, something like this will
appear in front of you. Click on the Like button at the top.
Click on it. You will
get many options here. Here you will
find the second option from the bottom, so click on it.
Click on the Do not use button,
three options will appear in front of you,
click here, click on online,
click on the one above you, here
you can see that payment online and
below you subscribe to the bank, you get an option, on
clicking this, the second option will roll in front of you from the
bottom,
after logging in, here you can see
enter loan account number and application
ID, for this you will get the option,
select and type, then click on it, on
clicking this, two options will appear in front of you,
loan account number, application ID,
some of the two are available with you,
click on it, I have a loan account number, click on
this,
after clicking, you have to enter your loan account number in the column below, then
I clicked,
here I typed my loan number, you
got the captcha code below, you will
fold the captcha code,
once you fill the captcha,
here you will tick on the time condition,
after fixing it, below you
get the option of submit, click on this,
click here  You can see that the
loan account is already disclosed and cancelled.
This means that the loan of this vehicle has been completely paid
and this vehicle is completely free.
No loan is activated on it.
If there was a loan on this vehicle, it would have appeared in front of you
here. There you
could have seen how much loan is there on this vehicle and how much
percentage is outstanding on it and how many
installments are left, it will appear in front of you here. You
can see it here. In this way,
you can see the loan of any two-wheeler.
If you liked the video, then
like and share the video and to
see such technical videos, do subscribe to our channel.